const STORE = [
    {//set1
        question: "What is the Generic name of Augmentin?",
        answers: [
           "A. Sumatriptan",
           "B. Amlodipine",
           "C. Penicillin",
          "D. Amoxicillin/Clavulanate",
              ],
        correctAnswer: "D. Amoxicillin/Clavulanate" ,
          }, 
        { //set2
          question: "Which is a common antibiotic?",
          answers: [
          "A. Zithromax",
          "B. Androgel",
          "C. Phentermine",
          "D. Fluoxetine", 
          ],
          correctAnswer: "A. Zithromax",
        }, 
        { //set3
         question: "Which of the following is considered a narcotic drug?",
          answers: [
          "A. Duragesic",
          "B. Misoprostol",
          "C. Epinephrine",
          "D. Prozac",
          ],
          correctAnswer: "A. Duragesic",
        },
        { //set4
          question: "What is the brand name of Sertraline?",
          answers: [
          "A. Synthroid",
          "B. Lunesta",
          "C. Zoloft" ,
          "D. Zestril", 
          ],
          correctAnswer: "C. Zoloft",
        },
        {//set5
        question: "What is Cymbalta used for?",
        answers: [
          "A. For weight loss",
          "B. As an antibiotic",
          "C. Treating depression",
          "D. As a birth control",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "C. Treating depression",
      },
      {//set 6
        question: "What is Actos (pioglitazone) used for?",
        answers: [
          "A. To lower blood glucose levels in the treatment of diabetes.",
          "B. As a diuretic",
          "C. As an anti-itch cream",
          "D. As a prenatal",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "A. To lower blood glucose levels in the treatment of diabetes.",
      },
      {//set7
        question: "What of the following is a birth control pill?",
        answers: [
          "A. Testosterone Cypionate",
          "B. Ovidrel",
          "C. Latuda",
          "D. Lessina",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "D. Lessina",
      },
      {//set8
        question: "What of the following is a brand of an inhaler",
        answers: [
          "A. Flonase",
          "B. Ventolin HFA",
          "C. Risperidone",
          "D. Effexor",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "B. Ventolin HFA",
      },
      {//set9
        question: "What is the generic name of Concerta?",
        answers: [
          "A. Citalopram",
          "B. Methylphenidate",
          "C. Clonazepam",
          "D. Atorvastin",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "B. Methylphenidate",
      },
      {//set10
        question: "Which of the following is a Schedule III Drug?",
        answers: [
          "A. Sudafed",
          "B. Robitussin",
          "C. Adderall",
          "D. Tylenol-Codeine",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "D. Tylenol-Codeine",
      },
    ];
    let questionNumber = 1;
    let score = 0;